Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/hanif-khoirulfathansyah-513839171 (LinkedIn) github.com/hanifkf12 (Portfolio)

Top Skills

Mobile Application Development
Web Development
Back-End Web Development

Certifications

Belajar Fundamental Aplikasi Android

Hanif Khoirul Fathansyah

Software Engineer di Elnusa Petrofin Yogyakarta

Summary

Experienced Mobile Application Developer & Backend Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Mobile Application Development & Backend development. Strong engineering professional with a Diploma focused in Informatika from Telkom University.

Experience

Elnusa Petrofin Software Engineer July 2020 - Present (2 years) Jakarta Selatan, Jakarta Raya, Indonesia

Outsourced Under Binar Talent Solutions

Binar Academy
Android Facilitator
January 2021 - March 2021 (3 months)
Online

Binar Academy Android Facilitator January 2020 - June 2020 (6 months) Tangerang

Toha Apps
Mobile Application Developer
December 2019 - February 2020 (3 months)

PMA Technology Mobile Application Developer October 2019 - November 2019 (2 months) Tangerang

Kodelokus

Back End Developer January 2019 - May 2019 (5 months) Bandung

PT LAUWBA TECHNO INDONESIA Web Developer June 2018 - August 2018 (3 months) Provinsi Yogyakarta , Indonesia

Education

Telkom University
Diploma, Informatika · (2016 - 2019)

SMA Negeri 1 Wonosari (July 2013 - June 2016)